I don't want nobody to get killed
我不願意看到有人被殺
I'll come and get you
我將來找尋你
I am always ready to fight
我一直準備與它們抗爭
So don't take all of the blame we were all swept away
所以別一個人承擔過錯 我們都在命運的洪流中
Don't take all of the weight. You always do
別一個人把重任扛在肩上 你總會這麼做
There will always be something you cannot control
人生不定 總會有些事你無法掌控
We will overcome. Your salvation has begun
而我們會克服一切 對你的救濟已經開始
No signs, no lights, such a mess all over
生命跡象為零 抬頭不見星光 腳下遍地混沌
Don't kill you hopes
然而不要扼殺你的希望
You make me realize who I need
你讓我察覺到我心底所求之人
I'll be there hold on
我會堅持在那裡
They'll change you somehow
可曾幾何時你已被他們改變
So where are you now?
而真正的你今在何方
I'll reach you by dawn
我會在黎明前找到你
The shadows appear，Illusions are born
身影浮現 幻影所生
The fallen angels you run with don't know
你所追逐的 你所不瞭解的墮落天使們
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
畢竟我們的痛苦讓我們更像是人類
Torn old sepia photographs show
被撕碎的紅褐色的照片上 所映出的
Our fragile precious world
是我們脆弱的而又美好的世界
Must discard it, respond to the call
必須拋棄舊世界 響應使命的召喚